[{"subjectID":"bvd09bpnor","prolificID":"5d8cef3c28e183001a335ab0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4073cbbee544bd383e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678934637,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"153","question":"What was the most recent gift you gave somebody? What was the reason or context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":8339,"timeElapsed":140034},{"subjectID":"bvd09bpnor","prolificID":"5d8cef3c28e183001a335ab0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4073cbbee544bd383e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678943590,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"153","question":"What was the most recent gift you gave somebody? What was the reason or context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":6,"rt":8949,"timeElapsed":148986},{"subjectID":"bvd09bpnor","prolificID":"5d8cef3c28e183001a335ab0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4073cbbee544bd383e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678948633,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"153","question":"What was the most recent gift you gave somebody? What was the reason or context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":2,"rt":5037,"timeElapsed":154029},{"subjectID":"bvd09bpnor","prolificID":"5d8cef3c28e183001a335ab0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4073cbbee544bd383e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678951241,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"153","question":"What was the most recent gift you gave somebody? What was the reason or context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":7,"rt":2604,"timeElapsed":156638},{"subjectID":"bvd09bpnor","prolificID":"5d8cef3c28e183001a335ab0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4073cbbee544bd383e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678954759,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"153","question":"What was the most recent gift you gave somebody? What was the reason or context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":3511,"timeElapsed":160156},{"subjectID":"bvd09bpnor","prolificID":"5d8cef3c28e183001a335ab0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4073cbbee544bd383e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678957076,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"153","question":"What was the most recent gift you gave somebody? What was the reason or context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":6,"rt":2310,"timeElapsed":162473},{"subjectID":"bvd09bpnor","prolificID":"5d8cef3c28e183001a335ab0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4073cbbee544bd383e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678959398,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"153","question":"What was the most recent gift you gave somebody? What was the reason or context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":2315,"timeElapsed":164795},{"subjectID":"bvd09bpnor","prolificID":"5d8cef3c28e183001a335ab0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4073cbbee544bd383e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678961814,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"153","question":"What was the most recent gift you gave somebody? What was the reason or context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":2409,"timeElapsed":167210},{"subjectID":"bvd09bpnor","prolificID":"5d8cef3c28e183001a335ab0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4073cbbee544bd383e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678964301,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"153","question":"What was the most recent gift you gave somebody? What was the reason or context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":4,"rt":2482,"timeElapsed":169698},{"subjectID":"bvd09bpnor","prolificID":"5d8cef3c28e183001a335ab0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4073cbbee544bd383e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678970341,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"74","question":"What’s a smell or sound that most people find unappealing but that you actually like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":4677,"timeElapsed":175738},{"subjectID":"bvd09bpnor","prolificID":"5d8cef3c28e183001a335ab0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4073cbbee544bd383e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678973612,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"74","question":"What’s a smell or sound that most people find unappealing but that you actually like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":3265,"timeElapsed":179009},{"subjectID":"bvd09bpnor","prolificID":"5d8cef3c28e183001a335ab0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4073cbbee544bd383e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678975775,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"74","question":"What’s a smell or sound that most people find unappealing but that you actually like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":2157,"timeElapsed":181171},{"subjectID":"bvd09bpnor","prolificID":"5d8cef3c28e183001a335ab0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4073cbbee544bd383e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678977715,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"74","question":"What’s a smell or sound that most people find unappealing but that you actually like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":1934,"timeElapsed":183112},{"subjectID":"bvd09bpnor","prolificID":"5d8cef3c28e183001a335ab0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4073cbbee544bd383e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678980238,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"74","question":"What’s a smell or sound that most people find unappealing but that you actually like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":2518,"timeElapsed":185635},{"subjectID":"bvd09bpnor","prolificID":"5d8cef3c28e183001a335ab0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4073cbbee544bd383e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678982448,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"74","question":"What’s a smell or sound that most people find unappealing but that you actually like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":2208,"timeElapsed":187845},{"subjectID":"bvd09bpnor","prolificID":"5d8cef3c28e183001a335ab0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4073cbbee544bd383e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678985186,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"74","question":"What’s a smell or sound that most people find unappealing but that you actually like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":2732,"timeElapsed":190582},{"subjectID":"bvd09bpnor","prolificID":"5d8cef3c28e183001a335ab0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4073cbbee544bd383e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678987601,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"74","question":"What’s a smell or sound that most people find unappealing but that you actually like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":2411,"timeElapsed":192998},{"subjectID":"bvd09bpnor","prolificID":"5d8cef3c28e183001a335ab0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4073cbbee544bd383e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678991273,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"74","question":"What’s a smell or sound that most people find unappealing but that you actually like?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":3668,"timeElapsed":196670},{"subjectID":"bvd09bpnor","prolificID":"5d8cef3c28e183001a335ab0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4073cbbee544bd383e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678998847,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"103","question":"What’s one thing about yourself you hope will never change?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":6441,"timeElapsed":204244},{"subjectID":"bvd09bpnor","prolificID":"5d8cef3c28e183001a335ab0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4073cbbee544bd383e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679000790,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"103","question":"What’s one thing about yourself you hope will never change?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":1938,"timeElapsed":206187},{"subjectID":"bvd09bpnor","prolificID":"5d8cef3c28e183001a335ab0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4073cbbee544bd383e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679004297,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"103","question":"What’s one thing about yourself you hope will never change?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":3502,"timeElapsed":209694},{"subjectID":"bvd09bpnor","prolificID":"5d8cef3c28e183001a335ab0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4073cbbee544bd383e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679006052,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"103","question":"What’s one thing about yourself you hope will never change?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":1751,"timeElapsed":211449},{"subjectID":"bvd09bpnor","prolificID":"5d8cef3c28e183001a335ab0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4073cbbee544bd383e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679008852,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"103","question":"What’s one thing about yourself you hope will never change?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":2796,"timeElapsed":214249},{"subjectID":"bvd09bpnor","prolificID":"5d8cef3c28e183001a335ab0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4073cbbee544bd383e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679010609,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"103","question":"What’s one thing about yourself you hope will never change?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":1752,"timeElapsed":216006},{"subjectID":"bvd09bpnor","prolificID":"5d8cef3c28e183001a335ab0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4073cbbee544bd383e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679014214,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"103","question":"What’s one thing about yourself you hope will never change?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3599,"timeElapsed":219610},{"subjectID":"bvd09bpnor","prolificID":"5d8cef3c28e183001a335ab0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4073cbbee544bd383e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679015839,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"103","question":"What’s one thing about yourself you hope will never change?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":1620,"timeElapsed":221235},{"subjectID":"bvd09bpnor","prolificID":"5d8cef3c28e183001a335ab0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4073cbbee544bd383e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679017777,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"103","question":"What’s one thing about yourself you hope will never change?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":1931,"timeElapsed":223174},{"subjectID":"bvd09bpnor","prolificID":"5d8cef3c28e183001a335ab0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4073cbbee544bd383e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679022163,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":3443,"timeElapsed":227560},{"subjectID":"bvd09bpnor","prolificID":"5d8cef3c28e183001a335ab0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4073cbbee544bd383e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679025464,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":3297,"timeElapsed":230861},{"subjectID":"bvd09bpnor","prolificID":"5d8cef3c28e183001a335ab0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4073cbbee544bd383e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679027895,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":6,"rt":2426,"timeElapsed":233291},{"subjectID":"bvd09bpnor","prolificID":"5d8cef3c28e183001a335ab0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4073cbbee544bd383e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679029495,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":1596,"timeElapsed":234892},{"subjectID":"bvd09bpnor","prolificID":"5d8cef3c28e183001a335ab0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4073cbbee544bd383e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679031550,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":5,"rt":2050,"timeElapsed":236947},{"subjectID":"bvd09bpnor","prolificID":"5d8cef3c28e183001a335ab0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4073cbbee544bd383e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679033612,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":5,"rt":2058,"timeElapsed":239009},{"subjectID":"bvd09bpnor","prolificID":"5d8cef3c28e183001a335ab0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4073cbbee544bd383e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679036185,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2569,"timeElapsed":241582},{"subjectID":"bvd09bpnor","prolificID":"5d8cef3c28e183001a335ab0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4073cbbee544bd383e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679037854,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":1665,"timeElapsed":243251},{"subjectID":"bvd09bpnor","prolificID":"5d8cef3c28e183001a335ab0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4073cbbee544bd383e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679047146,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":9286,"timeElapsed":252543},{"subjectID":"bvd09bpnor","prolificID":"5d8cef3c28e183001a335ab0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4073cbbee544bd383e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679049700,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":3,"rt":2550,"timeElapsed":255097},{"subjectID":"bvd09bpnor","prolificID":"5d8cef3c28e183001a335ab0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4073cbbee544bd383e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679054233,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"128","question":"Do you have a favorite poem? What is it? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":47,"rt":3617,"timeElapsed":259629},{"subjectID":"bvd09bpnor","prolificID":"5d8cef3c28e183001a335ab0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4073cbbee544bd383e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679057033,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"128","question":"Do you have a favorite poem? What is it? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":48,"rt":2796,"timeElapsed":262430},{"subjectID":"bvd09bpnor","prolificID":"5d8cef3c28e183001a335ab0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4073cbbee544bd383e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679059898,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"128","question":"Do you have a favorite poem? What is it? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":2861,"timeElapsed":265294},{"subjectID":"bvd09bpnor","prolificID":"5d8cef3c28e183001a335ab0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4073cbbee544bd383e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679062668,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"128","question":"Do you have a favorite poem? What is it? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":2767,"timeElapsed":268065},{"subjectID":"bvd09bpnor","prolificID":"5d8cef3c28e183001a335ab0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4073cbbee544bd383e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679064909,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"128","question":"Do you have a favorite poem? What is it? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":2238,"timeElapsed":270306},{"subjectID":"bvd09bpnor","prolificID":"5d8cef3c28e183001a335ab0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4073cbbee544bd383e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679066273,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"128","question":"Do you have a favorite poem? What is it? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":1359,"timeElapsed":271669},{"subjectID":"bvd09bpnor","prolificID":"5d8cef3c28e183001a335ab0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4073cbbee544bd383e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679068344,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"128","question":"Do you have a favorite poem? What is it? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":2066,"timeElapsed":273740},{"subjectID":"bvd09bpnor","prolificID":"5d8cef3c28e183001a335ab0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4073cbbee544bd383e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679070774,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"128","question":"Do you have a favorite poem? What is it? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":2425,"timeElapsed":276170},{"subjectID":"bvd09bpnor","prolificID":"5d8cef3c28e183001a335ab0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4073cbbee544bd383e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679073252,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"128","question":"Do you have a favorite poem? What is it? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":2473,"timeElapsed":278649},{"subjectID":"bvd09bpnor","prolificID":"5d8cef3c28e183001a335ab0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4073cbbee544bd383e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679077326,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"37","question":"What was the most difficult decision you ever had to make?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":3042,"timeElapsed":282723},{"subjectID":"bvd09bpnor","prolificID":"5d8cef3c28e183001a335ab0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4073cbbee544bd383e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679083498,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What was the most difficult decision you ever had to make?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":6168,"timeElapsed":288895},{"subjectID":"bvd09bpnor","prolificID":"5d8cef3c28e183001a335ab0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4073cbbee544bd383e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679086181,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"37","question":"What was the most difficult decision you ever had to make?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":2680,"timeElapsed":291578},{"subjectID":"bvd09bpnor","prolificID":"5d8cef3c28e183001a335ab0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4073cbbee544bd383e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679087413,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"37","question":"What was the most difficult decision you ever had to make?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":1228,"timeElapsed":292810},{"subjectID":"bvd09bpnor","prolificID":"5d8cef3c28e183001a335ab0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4073cbbee544bd383e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679090698,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"37","question":"What was the most difficult decision you ever had to make?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":3281,"timeElapsed":296095},{"subjectID":"bvd09bpnor","prolificID":"5d8cef3c28e183001a335ab0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4073cbbee544bd383e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679092881,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"37","question":"What was the most difficult decision you ever had to make?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":2180,"timeElapsed":298277},{"subjectID":"bvd09bpnor","prolificID":"5d8cef3c28e183001a335ab0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4073cbbee544bd383e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679097145,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"37","question":"What was the most difficult decision you ever had to make?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":4260,"timeElapsed":302542},{"subjectID":"bvd09bpnor","prolificID":"5d8cef3c28e183001a335ab0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4073cbbee544bd383e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679100828,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"37","question":"What was the most difficult decision you ever had to make?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3679,"timeElapsed":306225},{"subjectID":"bvd09bpnor","prolificID":"5d8cef3c28e183001a335ab0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4073cbbee544bd383e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679104019,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"37","question":"What was the most difficult decision you ever had to make?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3187,"timeElapsed":309416},{"subjectID":"bvd09bpnor","prolificID":"5d8cef3c28e183001a335ab0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4073cbbee544bd383e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679106390,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"37","question":"What was the most difficult decision you ever had to make?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":2363,"timeElapsed":311786},{"subjectID":"bvd09bpnor","prolificID":"5d8cef3c28e183001a335ab0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4073cbbee544bd383e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679115823,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":2,"rt":6001,"timeElapsed":321220},{"subjectID":"bvd09bpnor","prolificID":"5d8cef3c28e183001a335ab0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4073cbbee544bd383e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679117395,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":3,"rt":1568,"timeElapsed":322792},{"subjectID":"bvd09bpnor","prolificID":"5d8cef3c28e183001a335ab0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4073cbbee544bd383e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679119427,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":3,"rt":2027,"timeElapsed":324823},{"subjectID":"bvd09bpnor","prolificID":"5d8cef3c28e183001a335ab0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4073cbbee544bd383e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679121213,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":1782,"timeElapsed":326610},{"subjectID":"bvd09bpnor","prolificID":"5d8cef3c28e183001a335ab0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4073cbbee544bd383e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679123542,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2324,"timeElapsed":328938},{"subjectID":"bvd09bpnor","prolificID":"5d8cef3c28e183001a335ab0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4073cbbee544bd383e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679126458,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2913,"timeElapsed":331855},{"subjectID":"bvd09bpnor","prolificID":"5d8cef3c28e183001a335ab0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4073cbbee544bd383e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679128947,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2486,"timeElapsed":334344},{"subjectID":"bvd09bpnor","prolificID":"5d8cef3c28e183001a335ab0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4073cbbee544bd383e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679130722,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":1772,"timeElapsed":336119},{"subjectID":"bvd09bpnor","prolificID":"5d8cef3c28e183001a335ab0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4073cbbee544bd383e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679132509,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":1782,"timeElapsed":337906},{"subjectID":"bvd09bpnor","prolificID":"5d8cef3c28e183001a335ab0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4073cbbee544bd383e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679140587,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":7096,"timeElapsed":345984},{"subjectID":"bvd09bpnor","prolificID":"5d8cef3c28e183001a335ab0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4073cbbee544bd383e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679142824,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":2232,"timeElapsed":348221},{"subjectID":"bvd09bpnor","prolificID":"5d8cef3c28e183001a335ab0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4073cbbee544bd383e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679146732,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":3904,"timeElapsed":352129},{"subjectID":"bvd09bpnor","prolificID":"5d8cef3c28e183001a335ab0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4073cbbee544bd383e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679150164,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":3424,"timeElapsed":355560},{"subjectID":"bvd09bpnor","prolificID":"5d8cef3c28e183001a335ab0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4073cbbee544bd383e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679153779,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":3610,"timeElapsed":359176},{"subjectID":"bvd09bpnor","prolificID":"5d8cef3c28e183001a335ab0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4073cbbee544bd383e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679156006,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":2222,"timeElapsed":361403},{"subjectID":"bvd09bpnor","prolificID":"5d8cef3c28e183001a335ab0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4073cbbee544bd383e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679157958,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":1948,"timeElapsed":363355},{"subjectID":"bvd09bpnor","prolificID":"5d8cef3c28e183001a335ab0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4073cbbee544bd383e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679160072,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":2110,"timeElapsed":365468},{"subjectID":"bvd09bpnor","prolificID":"5d8cef3c28e183001a335ab0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4073cbbee544bd383e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679161582,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":1509,"timeElapsed":366979},{"subjectID":"bvd09bpnor","prolificID":"5d8cef3c28e183001a335ab0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4073cbbee544bd383e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679166963,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":49,"rt":4421,"timeElapsed":372360},{"subjectID":"bvd09bpnor","prolificID":"5d8cef3c28e183001a335ab0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4073cbbee544bd383e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679170513,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":3545,"timeElapsed":375910},{"subjectID":"bvd09bpnor","prolificID":"5d8cef3c28e183001a335ab0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4073cbbee544bd383e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679172599,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":2082,"timeElapsed":377996},{"subjectID":"bvd09bpnor","prolificID":"5d8cef3c28e183001a335ab0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4073cbbee544bd383e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679173843,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":1237,"timeElapsed":379240},{"subjectID":"bvd09bpnor","prolificID":"5d8cef3c28e183001a335ab0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4073cbbee544bd383e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679175650,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":46,"rt":1803,"timeElapsed":381047},{"subjectID":"bvd09bpnor","prolificID":"5d8cef3c28e183001a335ab0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4073cbbee544bd383e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679177811,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":45,"rt":2158,"timeElapsed":383208},{"subjectID":"bvd09bpnor","prolificID":"5d8cef3c28e183001a335ab0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4073cbbee544bd383e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679179846,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":2031,"timeElapsed":385243},{"subjectID":"bvd09bpnor","prolificID":"5d8cef3c28e183001a335ab0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4073cbbee544bd383e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679181774,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":5,"rt":1924,"timeElapsed":387171},{"subjectID":"bvd09bpnor","prolificID":"5d8cef3c28e183001a335ab0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4073cbbee544bd383e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679184054,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":2275,"timeElapsed":389451},{"subjectID":"bvd09bpnor","prolificID":"5d8cef3c28e183001a335ab0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4073cbbee544bd383e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679189526,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":4413,"timeElapsed":394923},{"subjectID":"bvd09bpnor","prolificID":"5d8cef3c28e183001a335ab0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4073cbbee544bd383e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679191570,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":2040,"timeElapsed":396967},{"subjectID":"bvd09bpnor","prolificID":"5d8cef3c28e183001a335ab0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4073cbbee544bd383e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679194008,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":2433,"timeElapsed":399405},{"subjectID":"bvd09bpnor","prolificID":"5d8cef3c28e183001a335ab0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4073cbbee544bd383e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679195405,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":1393,"timeElapsed":400802},{"subjectID":"bvd09bpnor","prolificID":"5d8cef3c28e183001a335ab0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4073cbbee544bd383e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679197325,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":45,"rt":1915,"timeElapsed":402722},{"subjectID":"bvd09bpnor","prolificID":"5d8cef3c28e183001a335ab0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4073cbbee544bd383e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679199372,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":2043,"timeElapsed":404769},{"subjectID":"bvd09bpnor","prolificID":"5d8cef3c28e183001a335ab0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4073cbbee544bd383e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679201057,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":1681,"timeElapsed":406454},{"subjectID":"bvd09bpnor","prolificID":"5d8cef3c28e183001a335ab0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4073cbbee544bd383e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679203025,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":1963,"timeElapsed":408422},{"subjectID":"bvd09bpnor","prolificID":"5d8cef3c28e183001a335ab0","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4073cbbee544bd383e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679206193,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":3164,"timeElapsed":411590}]